<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Outbreak analytics using R</title>
    <link>https://recon-escaide-2019.netlify.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Outbreak analytics using R</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://recon-escaide-2019.netlify.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview of the courses</title>
      <link>https://recon-escaide-2019.netlify.com/post/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recon-escaide-2019.netlify.com/post/overview/</guid>
      <description>Our two courses will be running in parallel ahead of ESCAIDE 2019 in Stockholm, on the 25-26th November 2019. See the practical information section for details on venue and timings.
Course #1 /// Introduction to epidemiological analysis using R Outline  Level: accessible to R beginners; see pre-requisites on the registration page. Capacity: 40 participants Summary: an introduction to using R for epidemiological analysis.  Course content A more detailed programme will be communicated closer to the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet the team</title>
      <link>https://recon-escaide-2019.netlify.com/post/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recon-escaide-2019.netlify.com/post/team/</guid>
      <description>Organisers  Amrish Baidjoe (RECON / EAN): researcher and consultant in health emergencies operational support, research and capacity building, president of the EAN and vice-president of RECON. Amrish has extensive field experience, and has spent the last months working with WHO on the Rohingya refugees crisis. Course organiser and trainer.
 Celine Barnadas (EAN): co-treasurer of EAN, Celine has a background in applied research and public health microbiology; she is currently working for the WHO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical information</title>
      <link>https://recon-escaide-2019.netlify.com/post/practical_info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recon-escaide-2019.netlify.com/post/practical_info/</guid>
      <description>Dates The courses will take place at the same time, in the two days leading up to ESCAIDE, on Monday 25 and Tuesday 26th November 2019. Precise time will be confirmed closer to the event.
Venue The event will be hosted at the European Centre for Disease Prevention and Control (ECDC) in Stockholm, Sweden. The exact address will be confirmed closer to the event.
Contact Any inquiry can be sent by email to Amrish Baidjoe by clicking on this link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration</title>
      <link>https://recon-escaide-2019.netlify.com/post/register/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recon-escaide-2019.netlify.com/post/register/</guid>
      <description>Application process How it works Applications will be made through the application form at the end of this page. Participants will be selected on a first arrived, first served basis. The process will work as follows:
 participant sends an application using the provided form if room is available, payment details are sent to the participant; otherwise, participant is put on the waiting list final confirmation is sent when payment is received; if no payment is received within 7 days, the application will be considered cancelled  Note that the two courses will be run in parallel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supporting partners</title>
      <link>https://recon-escaide-2019.netlify.com/post/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recon-escaide-2019.netlify.com/post/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>R Epidemics Consortium (RECON) The R Epidemics Consortium (RECON) is international not-for-profit, non-governmental organisation gathering experts in data science, modelling methodology, public health, operational epidemiology and software development to create the next generation of analytics tools for informing the response to disease outbreaks, health emergencies and humanitarian crises, using the R software and other free, open-source resources. RECON is currently the largest initiative for the development of R packages for epidemiological analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>